

1800 102 2558 | +91 9818882211







Senior Executive- CRM seeking roles in Software Deployment, Business Development, Client Relationships Management, Risk Management, New Business Generation, Customer Portfolio Management, Business Analysis, Pricing Analysis, Citrix, Xen App, Juniper

Current Designation: Senior Executive- CRM

Current Company: RLG India

Current Location: Delhi Pref. Location: Noida, Greater Noida, Delhi

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Role: Business Analyst

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Senior Executive- CRM, Business Analyst, Software Deployment, Business Development, Client Relationships Management, Risk Management, New Business Generation, Customer Portfolio Management, Business

Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 8 Month(s)

Highest Degree: MBAPGDM [Information Technology]

Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Analysis, Pricing Analysis, Citrix, Xen App, Juniper

Verified : Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Capable Relationship Manager experienced in developing customized solutions to meet wide-ranging customer needs. Strong collaborator and active listene with excellent verbal and written communication skills. Offering dynamic collaboration and decision making skills in a career spanning over 5+ years in IT & E-waste management industries.

Work Experience

RLG India as Senior Executive- CRM Sep 2020 to Till Date

Audit & Compliance- Ensure adherence to International standards of Business processes & functionalities. Key focus on Documentation Management in strict compliance with evolving CPCB Guidelines.

Data & MS Management- Manage and publish Client Dashboard, Pricing Analysis,

Inventory Tracker Management.

Business Analysis- Revenue Analysis & Renewal.

Business Presentations & Advisory- Weekly Internal & Monthly Business Review with

Team Management: Collaborate with Internal Team Members & liaise with Other Depts. to ensure B2B Customer Queries are resolved within stipulated timeframe.

Compunnel Software Group as Consultant- Strategy & Client Partnership Jul 2018 to Jul 2020

Collaborating with management on sales goals, planning, and forecasting; maintaining short- and long-term business development plans.

Identifying, qualifying and securing business opportunities; coordinating business generation activities; developing customized targeted sales strategies. Building business relationships with current and potential clients.

Creating and maintaining a list/database of prospect clients; maintaining database (CRM, Excel, etc.) of prospective client information.

IBM India Pvt. Ltd. as Practitioner Jan 2016 to Jun 2018

Handling Identity Access and Connectivity Issues, Software Deployment, Application Interface and environment architects.

Configuration of Outlook Exchange Accounts for Enterprise Accounts.

Identifying global outages which interrupt client services and escalate priority issues as per Client Specifications.

Important

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Responsible for incident identification, logging and categorization, escalation, routing the tickets to the 2nd and 3rd level support groups which includes vendor support as well. Managing and troubleshooting the Network & connectivity issues including web and software VPN (Citrix, XenApp, and Juniper) and Wi-Fi connectivity issues and configuration.

Responsible for planning and managing the operational activities for the team to ensure that the client service is in line with the customer requirements & achieve the SLA targets.

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Com (Commerce) from monad university in 2013

PG: MBA/PGDM (Information Technology) from Amity University in 2017

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
MS OFFICE		
CITRIX		
XENAPP		
JUNIPER		

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.